vandvshop.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | V & V ShopV & V Shop

Thanks for visiting [**vandvshop.com**](http://vandvshop.com/) and reviewing our privacy policy.

We are committed to protect all information that you share with us. We have accordingly developed this privacy policy to protect your personal information and keep it confidential. We follow stringent procedures to help protect the confidentiality, security, and integrity of data stored on our systems.

We collect information about you for 2 reasons: Firstly, to process your order and second, to provide you with the best possible service.

We will not e-mail you in the future unless you have given us your consent.

We will give you the chance to refuse any marketing email from us or from another trader in the future.

**The type of information we will collect about you includes:**

  * Your Name
  * Address
  * Phone Number
  * Email Address

We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent.

The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you by emailing us. If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly.

We may change this privacy policy at any time without notice and by updating this page. Please check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. Here is how we handle information about your visit to our Site.

The personal information which we hold will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law.

We may use technology to track the patterns of behavior of visitors to our site. This can include using a “ **cookie** ” which would be stored on your browser. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening.

The information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings.

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please e-mail your questions to us at **vandvshops@gmail.com**.
